ALEENA TRESA KP

WEB DEVELOPER

I am an energetic, ambitious person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task I undertake or situation that I am present with. As a post graduate with two years of experience in teaching and developing, I am excellent in working with others to achieve a certain objective on time and with excellence.



- KALATHIPARAMBIL HOUSE, OCHANTHURUTH PO, ERNAKULAM, VYPIN, PIN-682508, ERNAKULAM, India
- f facebook.com/aleena.tresa.5

- 08136840879
- in linkedin.com/in/aleena-tresa-kp-a22714210
- instagram.com/aleena_tresa

WORK EXPERIENCE

PYTHON TRAINER

Facein Technologies palarivattom

06/2023 - Present

Ernakulam

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Riss Technologies Kochi

07/2021 - 05/2023

Ernakulam

EDUCATION

MSC COMPUTER SCIENCE

KMM college of Arts & Science Thrikkakara

07/2019 - 07/2021

BSC COMPUTER SCIENCE

SN Arts & Science college Kedamangalam

08/2016 - 06/2019

Higher Secondary

St. Augustin's GHSS Kuzhupilly

High School

Little Flower High School Narakkal

SKILLS

HTML5

CSS

JAVASCRIPT

MYSQL

PYTHON- DJANGO, FLASK

PHP - LARAVEL

ANDROID STUDIO

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Helmet Violation System Using Deep Learning. it is a Web + Mobile Application developed by python flask framework and Android Studio.

Vehicle Hiring System it is a Web Application developed by Java.

RISS TECHNOLOGIES

- Gynaecology Hospital Management System. It is a web application developed by python django.
- Hospital Management System. it is a web application developed by PHP.
- Advanced E Commerce application. it was developed by Python flask framework and Android studio.

ACHIEVEMENTS

AWARDS

* Participated in workshop on agile mindset organized by cyrix *Participated in national webinar on deep neural networks.An efficient architecture for image classification organized by department of computer science application.

LANGUAGES

MALAYALAM

ENGLISH

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

HIND

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

MUSIC

TRAVELLING

PARTICIPATING IN SOCIAL ACTIVITIES